dirtywarez.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy - DirtyWarez

## 1\. Your Privacy 

  1. DirtyWarez is committed to protecting YOUR privacy. As such we do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to any companies or individuals. Unless otherwise specified DirtyWarez does not collect any personal information about our clients to sell to other companies. 
  2. You agree that You will provide accurate Personal Data and that you will update the same as and when necessary ensuring at all times that such information remains accurate. 

## 2\. Services 

  1. DirtyWarez respects your right to privacy. Any details that you give to us are voluntary. However if you wish to take advantage of Personalized services that we offer, you will need to provide certain information. 
  2. During the course of your visit to DirtyWarez our cookies will be placed on your system, so that your browsing experience may be more efficient and enjoyable. 

## 3\. Your Consent 

  1. By using DirtyWarez you consent to the collection and periodic use of your personal information set forth by DirtyWarez in this Privacy Policy. 
  2. DirtyWarez reserves the right at any time to change, update, alter or modify this privacy policy in any way without prior notice and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates. 
  3. Currently, DirtyWarez may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information only to reputable third-party vendors; however these statistics will at no time include any personal identifying information. 

## 4\. External Sites 

  1. DirtyWarez contains external links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please review the Privacy Policies on these external sites if you would like to read about their privacy practices. 

> **By reading this privacy policy you, the reader, agree to all terms and conditions set forth by this privacy policy and any changes it may entail. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us.**
